Guide to the Susan H. Douglas political Americana collection, [1783?]-1961.
Douglas, Susan H. Political Americana Collection, [1783?]-1961
- Series VIII. Pamphlets
  - Regular Republican Nominations / Regular Democratic Nominations, ca. 1888; 2214.PA0301 (Box 61)
  - Republican National Convention State Headquarters Directory, 1948; 2214.PA0302 (Box 61)
  - The A B C Of It, ca. 1912; 2214.PA0303a (Box 61)
  - Don'ts for Progressives, ca. 1912; 2214.PA0303b (Box 61)
  - The Labor and Money Questions: A New Catechism on Political Economy, 1874; 2214.PA0304 (Box 61)
  - Tippecanoe Club Records, Ward No. 1, Lowell, Massachusetts, 1840-1863; 2214.PA0306 (Box 166)
  - Democratic Inauguration Ball Invitation, 1845; 2214.PA0307 (Box 61)
  - Life of Col. Fremont, 1856; 2214.PA0308 (Box TBD)
  - The National Platforms of the Republican and Democratic Parties from 1856 to 1880 Inclusive, ca. 1880; 2214.PA0309 (Box 61)
  - Reform: For President, Samuel J. Tilden, ca. 1876; 2214.PA0310 (Box 61)
  - "Campaign Helps in Streamlined Garb" Folder, 1940; 2214.PA0311a (Box 93)
  - Willkie Letter to Grace E. Cano, 1940; 2214.PA0311b (Box 93)
  - "Win With Willkie" Bumper Sticker, ca. 1940; 2214.PA0311c (Box 93)
  - Telegram from Charles H. Griffith to Grace E. Cano, ca. 1940; 2214.PA0311d (Box 93)
  - We Want Willkie!, ca. 1940; 2214.PA0312 (Box 93)
  - The Democratic Book, 1936; 2214.PA0313a (Box TBD)
  - The Democratic National Convention, 1936; 2214.PA0313b (Box TBD)
  - The Independent Elector Plan of Illinois is Calling All Patriots, 1956; 2214.PA0314 (Box 61)
  - For America Recommends the Political Spare Tire, 1956; 2214.PA0315 (Box 61)
  - Your Personal Income Tax Could Be Eliminated!, 1956; 2214.PA0316 (Box 61)
  - Independent Candidates, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0317 (Box 61)
  - Why Choose Between Tweedle-Dee and Tweedle-Dum!, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0318 (Box 61)
  - Republican Speakers Handbook, 1956; 2214.PA0319 (Box 61)
  - A History of the Democratic Party, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0320 (Box 61)
  - Democratic Fact Book, 1956; 2214.PA0321 (Box 61)
  - Here We Go Again!, 1956; 2214.PA0322 (Box 61)
  - Election Year Argument Settler, 1956; 2214.PA0323 (Box 61)
  - Democratic Precinct Handbook: Official Manual, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0324 (Box 61)
  - Why We Need Senator Humphrey For Vice President, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0325 (Box 61)
  - Humphrey Helper's Handbook, ca. 1954; 2214.PA0326 (Box 61)
  - The Harriman Digest: How Others See The Candidate, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0327 (Box 61)
  - Averell Harriman: The Man and His Record, 1956; 2214.PA0328 (Box 62)
  - New York Acts for the Aging, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0329 (Box 62)
  - New York State Democratic Star, June 1956; 2214.PA0330 (Box 95)
  - For The Record: The Averell Harriman Farm Policy, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0331 (Box 62)
  - In The Tradition: Harriman Can Win!, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0332 (Box 62)
  - Harriman vs. The Kremlin, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0333 (Box 62)
  - Adlai E. Stevenson on Labor, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0334 (Box 62)
  - Stevenson The Man, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0335 (Box 62)
  - Stevenson ... A Friendly Man, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0336 (Box 62)
  - GOP Double-Dealing on Civil Rights, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0337 (Box 62)
  - Nixon?, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0338 (Box 62)
  - And They Say An Elephant Never Forgets, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0339 (Box 62)
  - But The Honeymoon Was Short!, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0340 (Box 62)
  - A Message From Eleanor Roosevelt, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0341 (Box 62)
  - Our Next President: Adlai E. Stevenson, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0342 (Box 62)
  - Our Foreign Policy: A Failure!, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0343 (Box 62)
  - Tax Cuts: For The Few But Not For You, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0344 (Box 62)
  - Why The Generals Are Scared!, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0345 (Box 62)
  - Oops! What Am I Saying?, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0346 (Box 62)
  - GOP Giveaways (It's a Steal!), ca. 1956; 2214.PA0347 (Box 62)
  - Your Candidate: Adlai E. Stevenson, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0348 (Box 62)
  - Which Party is Young In Heart?, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0349 (Box 62)
  - Who's In Charge Around Here?, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0350 (Box 62)
  - Shabby Deal for the Vets, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0351 (Box 62)
  - How The GOP Drives Small Business Out of Existence!, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0352 (Box 62)
  - What Happened to that "Great Crusade"?, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0353 (Box 62)
  - Come Back Tomorrow, Kids, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0354 (Box 62)
  - The Party For You, Not Just The Few, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0355 (Box 62)
  - Ike's Foreign Policy: A Failure!, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0356 (Box 62)
  - The Farmer Gets 'the Business', ca. 1956; 2214.PA0357 (Box 62)
  - The Ticket For You! And Here's Why, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0358 (Box 62)
  - Free Men Speak, July 1956; 2214.PA0359 (Box 95)
  - To Win: Adlai E. Stevenson, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0360 (Box 62)
  - The Ticket For You: Adlai Stevenson - Estes Kefauver, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0361 (Box 62)
  - How To Argue With A Republican, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0362 (Box 62)
  - The Farmers' Case Against Eisenhower, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0363 (Box 62)
  - All Business Needs Small Business, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0364 (Box 62)
  - Stevenson Bandwagon, August 13, 1956; 2214.PA0365 (Box 95)
  - Adlai Stevenson Says ... Democracy Belongs to Every American, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0366 (Box 62)
  - Adlai Stevenson On ..., ca. 1956; 2214.PA0367 (Box 62)
  - 1956 Republican Platform, 2214.PA0368 (Box 62)
  - Directory: Republican National Convention, San Francisco --, 1956; 2214.PA0369 (Box 62)
  - 1956 National Convention Handbook, 2214.PA0370 (Box 62)
  - Democratic National Convention, August 1956: Telephone Directory and Guide, 2214.PA0371 (Box 62)
  - The Democratic Platform, 1956; 2214.PA0372 (Box 62)
  - TV Guide, August 18-24, 1956; 2214.PA0373 (Box 62)
  - The Voter's Guide, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0374 (Box 62)
  - The Book Of Presidents, 1956; 2214.PA0375 (Box 62)
  - Pocket Reminder: Achievements of the Eisenhower-Nixon Republican Administration, 1953-1956, 2214.PA0376a (Box 62)
  - Pocket Reminder: Eisenhower-Republican Administration Achievements, 1953-1956, 2214.PA0376b (Box 62)
  - This Is The Man ... This Is His Family, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0377 (Box 62)
  - Re-Elect Ike and Dick: Vote Republican, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0378 (Box 62)
  - To Live and Let Live, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0379 (Box 62)
  - Republican Workers' Manual: Work and Win, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0380 (Box 62)
  - Citizens For Eisenhower-Nixon, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0381 (Box 62)
  - We Agree With You That..., ca. 1956; 2214.PA0382 (Box 62)
  - 7 Reasons Why YOU and Every VETERAN Should Vote For IKE, DICK and JACK, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0383 (Box 62)
  - Then and Now: Things Every Voter Should Remember, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0384 (Box 62)
  - Don't Break the Chain of Good Government ... Vote Republican All the Way!, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0385a (Box 62)
  - Here's How To Vote: Sample Office Type Ballot, Hamilton County, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0385b (Box 62)
  - Hamilton County Republican Judicial Candidates Bookmark, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0385c (Box 62)
  - New Jersey 1956 Calendar of Voting Information, 2214.PA0386 (Box 62)
  - You Make The Choice ..., ca. 1956; 2214.PA0387 (Box 62)
  - Ike in '56, 1956; 2214.PA0388 (Box 62)
  - Ohio Citizens For Eisenhower-Nixon Brochure, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0389 (Box 62)
  - Let's Look At ... Nixon, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0390 (Box 62)
  - The Truth About Nixon, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0391 (Box 62)
  - This Man Nixon, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0392 (Box 62)
  - Acceptance Address of the Vice President of the United States, Richard M. Nixon, 1956; 2214.PA0393 (Box 62)
  - Nixon: The Second Man?, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0394 (Box 62)
  - Win with Ike and Clean Government!, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0395 (Box 62)
  - Registration: First Big Step Toward Victory, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0396 (Box 62)
  - Forward With Eisenhower-Nixon, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0397 (Box 62)
  - Temporary Roll of Delegates and Alternate Delegates to Republican National Convention, 1956; 2214.PA0398 (Box 62)
  - Twenty-Sixth Republican National Convention: Order of Business, 1956; 2214.PA0399 (Box 62)
  - Eisenhower Bandwagon School In Madison Square Garden, 1956; 2214.PA0400a (Box 63)
  - Eisenhower Bandwagon Photograph, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0400b (Box 63)
  - Citizens for Eisenhower-Nixon Thank You Note Pad, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0401 (Box 63)
  - Citizens for Eisenhower-Nixon Advance, Issue No. 15, 1956; 2214.PA0402a (Box 63)
  - Citizens for Eisenhower-Nixon Advance, Issue No. 16, 1956; 2214.PA0402b (Box 63)
  - Plans Ideas Suggestions for Ike Day, October 13, 1956; 2214.PA0403a (Box 140)
  - Ike Day -- October 13, 1956, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0403b (Box 140)
  - Five Model Press Releases for Ike Day, October 13, 1956; 2214.PA0403c (Box 140)
  - "Happy Birthday Ike" Stationery Pad, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0403d (Box 140)
  - "Happy Birthday!, Ike" Portrait Poster, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0403e (Box 140)
  - Summary of Accomplishments: First Eisenhower Administration, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0404 (Box 63)
  - Food Prices Down - Wages Are Up!, 1956; 2214.PA0405 (Box 63)
  - The New York Republican Woman, October 1956; 2214.PA0406 (Box 93)
  - Gathering Of Our People Appreciation Dinner Program, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0407 (Box 93)
  - Civil Rights World Series: Souvenir Program and Score Card, 1956; 2214.PA0408 (Box 95)
  - Ike Has Kept The Peace, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0409 (Box 95)
  - Campaign Facts: Nineteen Fifty-Six, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0410 (Box 140)
  - Centennial Republican National Convention, San Francisco, August 1956; 2214.PA0411 (Box 140)
  - Eisenhower Paper Shopping Bag, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0412 (Box 95)
  - "Wouldn't You Know Harry Would Open That Hall Closet", ca. 1956; 2214.PA0413 (Box 63)
  - Proved Programs for Another Eisenhower Victory, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0414 (Box 63)
  - Prosperity and the Economic Health of the Nation, 1956; 2214.PA0416 (Box 63)
  - The Cabinet Speaks: Speeches by Members of the Cabinet, 1956; 2214.PA0417 (Box 63)
  - Text of a Speech by John Emmet Hughes, 1956; 2214.PA0418 (Box 63)
  - Acceptance Address of the President of the United States, 1956; 2214.PA0419 (Box 63)
  - New York State Citizens For Eisenhower-Nixon Leaflet, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0420 (Box 63)
  - A Candidate's Primer On How to Utilize Radio and Television Effectively, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0421 (Box 63)
  - Handbook for Women Workers: A Practical Guide for Campaign Organization, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0422 (Box 63)
  - National Citizens for Eisenhower Campaign Conference Schedule, 1956; 2214.PA0423 (Box 63)
  - "Herring" and Hiss: Strange Talk Of Mr. Truman, 1956; 2214.PA0424 (Box 63)
  - Nixon is Making Sense and Friends, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0425 (Box 63)
  - Rank and File Steelworker Says Labor Likes Ike, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0426 (Box 63)
  - Citizens for Eisenhower Advance, Issue No. 5, 1956; 2214.PA0427a (Box 63)
  - Citizens for Eisenhower Advance, Issue No. 6, 1956; 2214.PA0427b (Box 63)
  - Capitol Guide: Souvenir Guide For Capitol Hill, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0428 (Box 63)
  - Recipe for Better Living, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0429 (Box 63)
  - What The Democrats Think Of Each Other, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0430 (Box 63)
  - Unofficial Transcript of Address By President Dwight D. Eisenhower, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0431 (Box 63)
  - "It is the Highest Privilege of Every Citizen ...", ca. 1956; 2214.PA0432 (Box 63)
  - Summary of Highlights of Speech by Walter Williams, 1956; 2214.PA0433 (Box 63)
  - Labor and the Republican Party: A New Look, 1956; 2214.PA0434 (Box 63)
  - Speech Delivered by John A. Roosevelt, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0436 (Box 63)
  - Stevenson on Ike's Golf, 1956; 2214.PA0437 (Box 63)
  - National Citizens For Eisenhower Press Release, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0438 (Box 63)
  - Unofficial Transcript of Speech Delivered by Richard M. Nixon, 1956; 2214.PA0439 (Box 63)
  - "... There is No Room in America for Second-Class Citizenship for Anyone.", 1956; 2214.PA0440 (Box 95)
  - Women Want To Know!, 1956; 2214.PA0441a (Box 63)
  - When Women Work Sparks Fly!!, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0441b (Box 63)
  - Address Of George D. Flemmings, 1956; 2214.PA0442 (Box 63)
  - Unofficial Transcript of Speech Delivered By Dr. Gabriel Hauge, 1956; 2214.PA0443 (Box 63)
  - Unofficial Transcript of Speech of James C. Hagerty, 1956; 2214.PA0444 (Box 63)
  - National Citizens For Eisenhower Campaign Activities Manual, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0445 (Box 63)
  - The Who, What, Why, When, and How Of The Eisenhower Bandwagon Campaign in Connecticut, 1956; 2214.PA0447 (Box 63)
  - Notes and Suggestions Regarding Irving Berlin's Campaign Song, "Ike For Four More Years", 1956; 2214.PA0448 (Box 63)
  - Prescott S. Bush Campaign Correspondence Kit, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0449 (Box 93)
  - Political Book Matches, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0450 (Box 63)
  - Catalog of Novelty Items from the Ike Shop, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0451 (Box 63)
  - Waldman Button Co. Catalog & Price List, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0452 (Box 63)
  - Sensational Campaign Fund Raisers & Vote Getters!, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0453a (Box 63)
  - Harold K. Oleet & Bros., Inc. Order Form, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0453b (Box 63)
  - Campaign Materials Catalogue, 1956; 2214.PA0454 (Box 63)
  - A Magnificent Collection of Campaign Material, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0455 (Box 63)
  - An Important Campaign Memo!, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0456 (Box 63)
  - Emress Specialty Co. Flier & Price List, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0457 (Box 63)
  - "Official Ike (Autograph) Sun Visor" Order Form, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0458 (Box 63)
  - Republican National Committee Price List, September 21, 1956; 2214.PA0459a (Box 63)
  - Republican National Committee Price List, September 25, 1956; 2214.PA0459b (Box 63)
  - Republican National Committee Price List, October 2, 1956; 2214.PA0459c (Box 63)
  - Eisenhower For President Stamps Price List, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0460 (Box 63)
  - Metropolitan Printing Company Republican Campaign Material Price List, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0461 (Box 63)
  - Emress Speciality Company Price List, ca. 1948; 2214.PA0462a (Box 63)
  - Emress Speciality Company Price List, ca. 1952; 2214.PA0462b (Box 63)
  - The Republican Campaign Text-Book for, 1892; 2214.PA0463 (Box 166)
  - Eisenhower's Republican Administration Record, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0464 (Box 63)
  - Let's Talk About It!: Republicans Strengthen Dollar, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0465a (Box 63)
  - Let's Talk About It!: Republicans Cut Taxes For Everybody!, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0465b (Box 63)
  - Let's Talk About It!: Republican Defense Policies Mean a Safer America, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0465c (Box 63)
  - Let's Talk About It!: For The Farmer, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0465d (Box 63)
  - Let's Talk About It!: Working Men and Women Benefit from Republican Policies, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0465e (Box 63)
  - Let's Talk About It!: Peace With Justice, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0465f (Box 63)
  - Let's Talk About It!: "I am a Republican", ca. 1956; 2214.PA0465g (Box 63)
  - Ike And Dick Are Good For California, ca. 1956; 2214.PA0466 (Box 63)
  - Lives of Grant and Colfax, 1868; 2214.PA0467 (Box 166)
  - Letter regarding the 1880 Presidential Campaign, 2214.PA0468 (Box 63)
  - Young Men's Democratic Central Committee Meeting Announcement, 1860; 2214.PA0469 (Box 63)
  - The 1960 Conventions & Elections, 2214.PA0470a (Box 63)
  - National Convention & Election Handbook and Envelope, 1960; 2214.PA0470b (Box 63)
  - "The Man Who Stole Your Vote" Pamphlet and Envelope, ca. 1960; 2214.PA0470c (Box 63)
  - The Price You Pay For Graft!, ca. 1960; 2214.PA0470d (Box 63)
  - If Your Kids Could Vote, ca. 1960; 2214.PA0470e (Box 63)
  - The Next Four Years, ca. 1960; 2214.PA0470f (Box 63)
  - Republican National Convention Pass Out Check, 1960; 2214.PA0470g (Box 63)
  - Presidential Election Handbook, ca. 1960; 2214.PA0470h (Box 63)
  - Twenty-Seventh Republican National Convention: Order of Business, 1960; 2214.PA0471 (Box 63)
  - Grass-Roots Polls and Primaries Prove It: Americans Know Dick Nixon is the Man the Nation Needs!, 1960; 2214.PA0472a (Box 63)
  - Dick Nixon Club Pamphlet, ca. 1960; 2214.PA0472b (Box 63)
  - Thumbnail Biography of Richard M. Nixon, ca. 1960; 2214.PA0472c (Box 63)
  - Ten Reasons Why We Should Elect Nixon President, ca. 1960; 2214.PA0472d (Box 63)
  - "There is No Man in the History of America ...", 1960; 2214.PA0472e (Box 63)
  - Why America Needs Richard Nixon, ca. 1960; 2214.PA0472f (Box 63)
  - Dick Nixon Likes People, and ... the People Like Dick Nixon, ca. 1960; 2214.PA0472g (Box 63)
  - Richard Nixon: A Political and Personal Portrait, 1960; 2214.PA0472h (Box TBD)
  - Nixon "Postcards-For-Nixon" Portrait Postcard, ca. 1960; 2214.PA0472j (Box 63)
  - Republican Jewelry ... With Distinction, ca. 1960; 2214.PA0473a (Box 63)
  - Thomas A. Smith Association "Win with Kennedy" Handbill, ca. 1960; 2214.PA0473b (Box 63)
  - Do Your Trumpeting Far and Wide with Green Duck's Complete Campaign Service!, ca. 1960; 2214.PA0473c (Box 63)
  - Let Green Duck Come To The Aid Of The Party, ca. 1960; 2214.PA0473d (Box 63)
  - A Magnificent Collection of Campaign Material, ca. 1960; 2214.PA0473e (Box 63)
  - Ballyhoo Antenna Flag Advertisements & Envelope, ca. 1960; 2214.PA0473f (Box 63)
  - Attention all Republican Clubs - Organizations - Committees, ca. 1960; 2214.PA0473g (Box 63)
  - Leadership for the 60's: Kennedy for President, ca. 1960; 2214.PA0474a (Box 95)
  - A Look at the Record from Labor's Viewpoint, ca. 1960; 2214.PA0474b (Box 95)
  - Reformation Sunday Leaflet & Button, 1960; 2214.PA0475a (Box 63)
  - A Brief History of The Reformation, ca. 1960; 2214.PA0475b (Box 63)
  - A Roman Catholic President: How Free From Church Control?, ca. 1960; 2214.PA0475c (Box 63)
  - The Republican Party: Its History in Brief, 1952; 2214.PA0476 (Box 63)
  - An Arrangement of Medals and Tokens, 1862; 2214.PA0477a (Box 63)
  - The Medals and Tokens of Henry Clay, ca. 1918; 2214.PA0477b (Box 63)
  - Election Medals of the Campaign of 1844, 1943; 2214.PA0477c (Box 63)
  - Medalets of the Presidential Campaign of 1848, 1948; 2214.PA0477d (Box 63)
  - George Washington Medals of 1889, 1949; 2214.PA0477e (Box 63)
  - Catalogue: American Scenes And Events On Textiles, 1941; 2214.PA0478 (Box 169)
- Series IX. Parades
  Parades: This series contains a variety of artifacts that were carried in political parades or other public events. They range in size from small pennants to very large parade banners, and in form from replica axes and guns to hats and helmets, kerosene "torch lights", lanterns, and walking sticks. Mrs. Douglas also included a limited amount of materials advertising parade items in this category. There is significant overlap between the "Parades" and "Wearing Apparel" categories.
  - Thomas Dewey for President Pennant, ca. 1948; 2214.PD0001 (Box 141)
  - Harry Truman for President Pennant, ca. 1948; 2214.PD0002 (Box 141)
  - Eisenhower Inaugural Pennant, ca. 1953; 2214.PD0003 (Box 141)
  - Bryan-Kern Campaign Pennant, ca. 1908; 2214.PD0004 (Box 82)
  - Vote Democratic Pennant, ca. 1948; 2214.PD0005 (Box 82)
  - Vote Republican Pennant, ca. 1948; 2214.PD0006 (Box 82)
  - I Like Ike for President Pennant, ca. 1952; 2214.PD0007 (Box 82)
  - Stassen Pennant, ca. 1948; 2214.PD0008 (Box 82)
  - Dewey Pennant, ca. 1948; 2214.PD0009 (Box 82)
  - Eisenhower Inaugural Pennant, ca. 1953; 2214.PD0010 (Map-case -)
  - Eisenhower Inaugural Pennant, ca. 1953; 2214.PD0011 (Map-case -)
  - Harrison and Reid Club Banner, ca. 1892; 2214.PD0012 (Box 153)
  - Clay-Frelinghuysen Parade Streamer, ca. 1844; 2214.PD0013 (Box 150)
  - Cleveland-Thurman "Let The Eagle Scream!" Parade Banner, ca. 1888; 2214.PD0014 (Box TBD)
  - Cleveland-Hendricks Parade Banner, ca. 1884; 2214.PD0015 (Box TBD)
  - McKinley-Hobart Pennant, ca. 1896; 2214.PD0016 (Box 153)
  - Garfield "From the Tow Path to the White House" Banner, ca. 1880; 2214.PD0017 (Box 153)
  - Garfield-Arthur Pennant, ca. 1880; 2214.PD0018 (Map-case -)
  - Cleveland-Thurman Street Banner (Partial), ca. 1888; 2214.PD0019 (Box TBD)
  - Benjamin Harrison Saddlecloth, ca. 1888; 2214.PD0020 (Box 150)
  - Republican Elephant Cloth Bag, 1952; 2214.PD0021 (Box 150)
  - Benjamin Harrison Portrait Head Walking Stick, ca. 1888; 2214.PD0022 (Box 119)
  - Bryan-Stevenson Torch Light Walking Stick, ca. 1900; 2214.PD0023 (Box 119)
  - Bryan Portrait Head Walking Stick, ca. 1896; 2214.PD0024 (Box 119)
  - Bryan "The People's Choice" Portrait Head Walking Stick, ca. 1896; 2214.PD0025 (Box 120)
  - Henry Clay Portrait Head Walking Stick, ca. 1844; 2214.PD0026 (Box 118)
  - Cleveland Photographic Portrait Walking Stick, ca. 1884; 2214.PD0027 (Box 121)
  - Cleveland "Honest Ballot Box" Torch Light, ca. 1884; 2214.PD0028 (Box 55)
  - Cleveland Portrait Head Walking Stick, ca. 1884; 2214.PD0029 (Box 121)
  - Cleveland-Thurman Portrait Paper Balloon Lantern, ca. 1888; 2214.PD0030 (Box 220)
  - Republican Inscribed Tin Horn, 1872-1880; 2214.PD0031 (Box 64)
  - Grant Portrait Head Walking Stick, ca. 1868; 2214.PD0033 (Box 121)
  - Grant-Wilson Collapsible Paper Lantern, ca. 1872; 2214.PD0034a (Box 66)
  - Grant-Wilson Collapsible Paper Lantern, ca. 1872; 2214.PD0034b (Box 66)
  - Eisenhower "Our President" Portrait Street Banner, ca. 1953; 2214.PD0035 (Box 150)
  - "Welcome"/ Presidential Seal Street Banner, ca. 1953; 2214.PD0036 (Box TBD)
  - Presidential Seal Street Banner, ca. 1953; 2214.PD0037 (Box TBD)
  - McKinley-Hobart Miniature Parade Banner, 1896; 2214.PD0038 (Box 139)
  - Grant "Union For Ever" Collapsible Paper Lantern, ca. 1868; 2214.PD0039 (Box 66)
  - Benjamin Harrison-Reid Portrait Top Hat, 1892; 2214.PD0040a (Box 161)
  - Benjamin Harrison-Reid Portrait Top Hat, 1892; 2214.PD0040b (Box 163)
  - Harrison-Morton Portrait Paper Balloon Lantern, ca. 1888; 2214.PD0041 (Box 220)
  - Benjamin Harrison "Same Old Hat" Torch Light, ca. 1888; 2214.PD0042 (Box 55)
  - Lincoln Wooden Parade Axe, 1860; 2214.PD0043 (Map-case EE-9)
  - Rublee Campaign Banner Co. Flier, ca. 1908; 2214.PD0044 (Box 97)
  - Political Goods Price List, ca. 1876; 2214.PD0045 (Box 94)
  - Cleveland Rooster Parade Sign and Card, ca. 1893; 2214.PD0046 (Box TBD)
  - Hayes-Wheeler Metal and Paper Lantern Candle Holder, 1876; 2214.PD0047 (Box 65)
  - Hayes-Wheeler Metal and Paper Lantern Candle Holder, 1876; 2214.PD0048 (Box 65)
  - McKinley "Our Champion" Portrait Head Walking Stick, ca. 1896; 2214.PD0049 (Box 120)
  - McKinley "Protection / 1896" Portrait Head Walking Stick, 2214.PD0050 (Box 120)
  - McKinley "Protection / Prosperity" Portrait Head Walking Stick, ca. 1896; 2214.PD0051 (Box 121)
  - McKinley-Hobart Torch Light Walking Stick, ca. 1896; 2214.PD0052 (Box 119)
  - McKinley "Our Next President" Portrait Head Walking Stick, ca. 1896; 2214.PD0053 (Box 120)
  - Tilden-Hendricks Collapsible Paper Lantern, ca. 1876; 2214.PD0054 (Box 66)
  - Theodore Roosevelt Wooden Parade Gun, ca. 1904; 2214.PD0055 (Box TBD)
  - Political Campaign Banners, Streamers, Pictures, ca. 1908; 2214.PD0056 (Box 102)
  - Special Price List of Campaign Goods, ca. 1908; 2214.PD0057 (Box TBD)
  - Spherical Tin Torch Light, ca. 1884; 2214.PD0058 (Box 54)
  - Rectangular Torch Light with Four Wick Tubes, ca. 1860-1904; 2214.PD0059 (Box 14)
  - Parade Lantern with Red Glass Globe, ca. 1860-1904; 2214.PD0060 (Box 55)
  - Pole Handle for Torch Light, ca. 1860-1904; 2214.PD0060a (Map-case -)
  - Tin Torch Light with Tapering Base, ca. 1860-1904; 2214.PD0061 (Box 54)
  - Ovoid Tin Torch Light, ca. 1860-1904; 2214.PD0062 (Box 54)
  - Item apparently not donated to Cornell University, 2214.PD0063 (Box -)
  - Spherical, Swivel-mounted Brass and Tin Torch Light, ca. 1860-1904; 2214.PD0064 (Box 54)
  - Small Cone-Shaped Tin Torch Light, ca. 1860-1904; 2214.PD0065 (Box 55)
  - Black-painted Cylindrical Torch Light, ca. 1860-1904; 2214.PD0066 (Box 54)
  - Torch Light Helmet, ca. 1884; 2214.PD0067 (Box 48)
  - Torch Light Helmet, ca. 1888; 2214.PD0068 (Box 53)
  - Torch Light Helmet, ca. 1892; 2214.PD0069 (Box 49)
  - Elephant Head Walking Stick, ca. 1948; 2214.PD0070 (Box 118)
  - William Henry Harrison Log Cabin Walking Stick, ca. 1840; 2214.PD0071 (Box 118)
  - Benjamin Harrison-Morton Walking Stick, ca. 1888; 2214.PD0072 (Box 118)
  - Cleveland Portrait Head Walking Stick, ca. 1884; 2214.PD0073 (Box 121)